<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
    <changelog>
        <element>jtpositionfinder</element>
        <type>plugin</type>
        <version>1.0.4</version>
        <fix>
            <item>Improved search relevance so exact template element matches, such as Cassiopeia, are listed before partial matches such as Cassiopeia Extended.</item>
            <item>Clarified search wording to show that users search template groups and select module position values.</item>
            <item>Changed the selected position badge text to Current value to avoid confusion when the same module position exists in multiple template groups.</item>
            <item>Added template element badges to template group headings for clearer distinction between similar template names.</item>
        </fix>
        <update>
            <item>Updated administrator JavaScript and language strings for clearer template group search behavior.</item>
        </update>
    </changelog>
    <changelog>
        <element>jtpositionfinder</element>
        <type>plugin</type>
        <version>1.0.3</version>
        <security>
            <item>Added LICENSE.txt to the install package for GPL/JED compliance.</item>
            <item>Hardened templateDetails.xml parsing with libxml internal errors and LIBXML_NONET.</item>
        </security>
        <fix>
            <item>Removed automatic plugin enable installer script from the install package.</item>
            <item>Added modal double-open protection and safer body modal-open handling.</item>
            <item>Added explicit manifest element value and synchronized asset versions.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>
    <changelog>
        <element>jtpositionfinder</element>
        <type>plugin</type>
        <version>1.0.2</version>
        <update>
            <item>Added Joomla update server metadata to the extension manifest.</item>
            <item>Added Joomla changelog URL to the extension manifest and update stream.</item>
            <item>Prepared official update stream metadata for GitHub Releases distribution.</item>
        </update>
    </changelog>
    <changelog>
        <element>jtpositionfinder</element>
        <type>plugin</type>
        <version>1.0.0</version>
        <update>
            <item>Initial stable release of JT Position Finder.</item>
            <item>Added template-grouped position browsing with search, usage badges and custom position input.</item>
        </update>
    </changelog>
</changelogs>
